thegooddrugsguide.com 2012-02-05

# Privacy Policy

By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use and Disclaimer, Mybodypart.com collects certain information about you that you specifically and knowingly provide to us, such as your user name, email address, name or mailing address. In addition, we may track how you use this Site and relate it to the information you have provided to us. If you wish to be notified of the use of such tracking software and/or disable such software, your browser may offer this feature by means of its options or preferences menu. 

The above-described information (Personally-Identifying Information) may be used by Mybodypart.com to personalize and enhance your use of this Site, including the marketing and promotion of certain products and services that might be of interest to you. Your use of this Site is consent to the foregoing use of your Personally-Identifying Information by Mybodypart.com 

Mybodypart.com also may share your Personally-Identifying Information with select companies and organizations for their own marketing and promotional use. While Mybodypart.com seeks to share Personally-Identifying Information with companies that follow appropriate privacy policies, it does not bear any responsibility for the actions and policies of such third parties. If you wish that we not share your Personally-Identifying Information with third parties, you may "opt out" by emailing us with such request. 

You should be aware that any Personally-Identifying Information, such as your user name and email address, as well as any other information that you post on a bulletin board, share in a "chat room," or otherwise specifically and knowingly disclose by use of the site, may be directly collected and used by third parties. Therefore, you may be subject to unsolicited email as a result of your disclosure of such information. You should have no expectation of privacy with respect to your communications through the forums, or profile should you choose to list this information.

  1. Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like TheGoodDrugsGuide.com. Based in the United States of America, our principal activity is the delivery of informational content and business listing information.
  2. Our Website Privacy Policy Statement covers TheGoodDrugsGuide.com, its subsidiaries and any of its websites accessible via the primary websites listed below: 

  3. You can access our website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.
  4. We collect the personal information that you may volunteer while using our services.
  5. We do not collect information about our visitors from sources outside of TheGoodDrugsGuide.com, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.
  6. We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than email marketing and than that indicated on the Web pages where the information is requested or collected.
  7. If we wish to use your personal information for a new purpose, we will contact you first for permission.
  8. Except as requested by you, we do not disclose your personal information to other organizations.

## Website Security Policy

TheGoodDrugsGuide.com is committed to complying with all federal, state, and local laws, as well as applicable regulations, standards, and guidelines established by government agencies and accepted accrediting organizations.

We will provide a secure transmission method for you to send us personal information, including:

  * Identifiers (such as social security numbers, credit card details, website password) 

While such secure transmission methods provide reasonable protections against unauthorized access, if you have concerns regarding the transmission of sensitive information (such as contact or medical information), you should consider using non-electronic communication methods. 

We have implemented security policies, rules, and reasonable technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

  * Unauthorized access 
  * Improper use or disclosure 
  * Unauthorized modification 
  * Unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors who have access to, and are associated with, the processing of personal information are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal information.

Top

## Email Privacy Disclaimer

TheGoodDrugsGuide.com will use reasonable means to protect the privacy of your information sent by e-mail. However, because of the risks outlined below, TheGoodDrugsGuide.com cannot guarantee that email communications will be confidential. Additionally, TheGoodDrugsGuide.com will not be liable in the event that you or anyone else inappropriately uses your e-mail. TheGoodDrugsGuide.com will not be liable for improper disclosure of your information that is not caused by TheGoodDrugsGuide.com's intentional misconduct. 

Top

## Email Risks and Your Responsibilities

At the discretion of TheGoodDrugsGuide.com, its staff, physicians and agents and upon your agreement to the terms outlined within this consent form, you may use email to communicate with TheGoodDrugsGuide.com. These e-mails may contain your personal health information. If you decide to use email to communicate with TheGoodDrugsGuide.com, you should be aware of the following risks and/or your responsibilities:

  1. As the Internet is not secure or private, unauthorized people may be able to intercept, read and possibly modify email you send or are sent by TheGoodDrugsGuide.com.
  2. You must protect your email account, password and computer against access by unauthorized people.
  3. Since email can be used to spread viruses, some which cause email messages to be sent to people who you do not intend to send email messages to, you should install and maintain virus protection software on your PC.
  4. Since e-mails can be copied, printed and forwarded by people to whom you send e-mails, you should be careful regarding to whom you send e-mails.
  5. As your employer may claim ownership of, or the right to access, the email account issued to you by your e-mail, you should avoid using an employer issued email account to communicate with TheGoodDrugsGuide.com.

Top

## Conditions for the Use of Email

By consenting to the use of email with TheGoodDrugsGuide.com, you agree that:

  1. TheGoodDrugsGuide.com may forward emails as appropriate for treatment, and other related reasons. As such, TheGoodDrugsGuide.com staff members, other than the recipient, may have access to emails that you send. Such access will only be to such persons who have a right to access your email to provide services to you. Otherwise, TheGoodDrugsGuide.com will not, otherwise, forward emails to independent third parties without your prior written consent, except as authorized or required by law.
  2. You should carefully word your email messages so the information provided clearly, yet briefly, describes the information you intend to convey. 
  3. You are responsible for correcting any unclear or incorrect information.
  4. TheGoodDrugsGuide.com reserves the right to save your email and include your email or information contained within your email in your medical record.
  5. Emails may not be the only form of communication that TheGoodDrugsGuide.com will use to communicate with you. Additionally, TheGoodDrugsGuide.com may decide that it is not in your best interest to continue to communicate with you by email. In such case, TheGoodDrugsGuide.com will notify that it no longer intends to communicate with you by email.

Top

## Contacting Us

Should you have any questions regarding these Terms of Use, the Privacy Statement, or the collection, retention, or management of any information on this website, please contact us using this form.

Top
